#04 "The Untainted Cleric"
Lucky Lecher
Only takes 300 LP to get!
Noir Stardia   Lv.35
LP.2270
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Skills [Great Sage] [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow]
Skills [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet] [Discerning Eye]
Skills [Headache Immunity] [Pocket Dimension (Grade C)]
Skills [Improved Back Step] [Passive Defense]
Skills [Shoulder Rub] [Lucky Lecher]
Noir Stardia   Lv.35
LP.1970
Lucky Lecher
Causes erotic situations to occur
with nearby members of the opposite sex.
Spent
"rarely"
"Skill will not trigger during serious situations."
Species: Half-elf
Age: 17
Occupation: Cleric/Adventurer
Skills: [Magical Firearms (Grade B)] [Energizing Shot]
Skills: [Healing Shot] [Cowardice] [Lift Curse]
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Luna Heela   Lv.35
Skill: Lift Curse
Skill: Erases curse skills. However, the user's
Skill: lifespan is reduced in proportion to
Skill: the strength of the curse.
I don't
wanna die
Skill
[Cowardice]
Cowardice
Depleting mana or receiving
intense attacks may make the
user even more cowardly.
[Lift Curse]
Erases curse skills.
However, the user's lifespan is reduced in
proportion to the strength of the curse.
Uses
Necessary
User's lifespan
is reduced.
Lifespan
Finances
rels
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
[Lift Curse]
However, the user's lifespan is reduced in
Erases curse skills.
proportion to the strength of the curse.
However, the user's finances are reduced in
Uses
Necessary
Lifespan
Finances
rels
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
User's finances
are reduced.
Lacking
Alice Theater
#05 "The Future of This Harem"
Illustration: Fuumi